# **Reden Sanchez**

Full Stack Software Developer

Cagayan de Oro City, Philippines +639928002836 redensanchez.jobs@gmail.com

#### **BACKGROUND**

Front end developer with 7+ years of experience building React applications, creating well-written and testable code.

Passionate about learning and understanding any infrastructure to deliver work from development to release.

Knowledgeable with Git, Redis, MongoDB, SQL Server, NodeJS, CLI and comfortable working with tools such as Visual Studio Code, Android Studio, Yarn, Npm to name a few.

Enjoys the challenge of learning and figuring out a solution to a problem, mostly setting up and providing proof of concept before diving deep into implementation.

### **EXPERIENCE**

## EMAPTA, MAKATI - ReactJS Developer

Feb 2019 - Jun 2023

Develop and release new features based on product (PRD) and software design decision (SDD)

# **CloudEmployee**, MAKATI — Full Stack Developer

Nov 2018 - Feb 2020

Implemented React Apollo to support GraphQL backend

# **ARMSTEAD Inc**, Nevada USA — Full Stack Developer

May 2015 - Oct 2018

Implement e-commerce API for buying and selling numerous dog breeds.

## **EDUCATION**

## **STI College**, Cagayan de Oro

Jun 2009 - Oct 2013

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology. Non-degree holder

### **SKILLS**

**JavaScript** 

HTML & CSS

React & React Native

**NodeIS** 

**Typescript** 

CI/CD